// An array of objects containing questions, answer options, and correct answers

const questions = [
    {
      question: "Javascript is an _______ language.",
      options: ["Object-Oriented", "Object-Based", "Procedural", "None of the above"],
      correctAnswer: "Object-Oriented",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      options: ["var", "let", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
      correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        options:["getElementById()", "getElementsByClassName", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
    },
    {
        question:"How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        options:["const", "let", "var", "constant"],
        correctAnswer: "const",
    },
    {
        question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        options: ["<javascript>", "<js>", "<script>", "<scripting>"],
        correctAnswer: "script",
    },
    {
        question:"JavaScript code can be written in ____.",
        options: ["JavaScript file (.js file)", "HTML document directly", "Both A and B", "In style sheets (.css file)"],
        correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
    },
    {
        question: "JavaScript ignores?",
        options: ["newlines", "tabs", "spaces", "All of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
        question: "Which property is used to define the HTML content to an HTML element with a specific id?",
        options: ["innerText","innerContent","elementText","innerHTML"],
        correctAnswer: "innerHTML",
    },
    {
        question: "Which JavaScript method is used to write HTML output?",
        options: ["document.write()", "response.write()", "write()", "document.output()"],
        correctAnswer: "document.write()",
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, single line comment begins with ___.",
        options: ["#", "$", "//", "/*"],
        correctAnswer: "//",
    },
  ];